const STORE = [{
    question: 'Which is the oldest restaurant in Portland?',
    answers: [
        `Besaw's`,
        `Huber's Cafe`,
        `Mother's Bistro & Bar`,
        `Jake's Famous Crawfish`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `Huber's Cafe`,
    gif: 'insert URL here',
    alt: 'describe URL here'
}, {
    question: 'Which TV show was NOT primarily filmed in Portland?',
    answers: [
        'Backstrom',
        'Grimm',
        'The X-Files',
        'Bates Motel'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The X-Files',
    gif: 'insert URL here',
    alt: 'describe URL here'
}, {
    question: 'What was the name of the original owner of the Pittock Mansion?',
    answers: [
        'Harold Pittock',
        'Harvey Pittock',
        'Henry Pittock',
        'Harry Pittock'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Henry Pittock',
    gif: 'insert URL here',
    alt: 'describe URL here'
}, {
    question: 'What is the name of the large Portland waterfront festival, usually held from the end of May until mid-June?',
    answers: [
        'Jazz Festival',
        'Keep Portland Weird Festival',
        'Beerfest NW',
        'Rose Festival'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Rose Festival',
    gif: 'insert URL here',
    alt: 'describe URL here'
}, {
    question: 'In which year did the Portland Trail Blazers win the NBA Championship?',
    answers: [
        '1969',
        '1988',
        '1999',
        '1977'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '1977',
    gif: 'insert URL here',
    alt: 'describe URL here'
}, {
    question: 'What is the name of the collective group of fans of the Portland Timbers?',
    answers: [
        `The Timber's Army`,
        'The Forest',
        'The Timber Armada',
        'The Lumberjacks'
    ],
    correctAnswer: `The Timber's Army`,
    gif: 'insert URL here',
    alt: 'describe URL here'
}, {
    question: 'Which coffee company was founded in Portland?',
    answers: [
        'Starbucks',
        `Pete's Coffee`,
        'Dutch Bros.',
        'Stumptown'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Stumptown',
    gif: 'insert URL here',
    alt: 'describe URL here'
}, {
    question: 'Portland has a dormant volcano within its city limits. What is its name?',
    answers: [
        'Mt. Hood',
        'Mt. Tabor',
        'Powell Butte',
        'The West Hill'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Mt. Tabor',
    gif: 'insert URL here',
    alt: 'describe URL here'
}, {
    question: 'Which pint-sized world record does Portland hold?',
    answers: [
        `The world's smallest park`,
        `The world's smallest brewery`,
        `The world's smallest ferris wheel`,
        `The world's smallest playable piano`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `The world's smallest park`,
    gif: 'insert URL here',
    alt: 'describe URL here'
}, {
    question: `In 2007 at Portland's Waterfront Park, a news-clip featuring 10-year old "Zombie Boy" Jonathon Ware went viral when he responded to a reporter with which statement?`,
    answers: [
        'I like poodles',
        'I like sweaters',
        'I like turtles',
        'I like puddles'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'I like turtles',
    gif: 'insert URL here',
    alt: 'describe URL here'
}];

/* choose incorrect gif*/
// rename gif to img url